{
    "id": "5257d038d7c342ed9614a168a7cf23f8",
    "title": "Words Commonly Confused | Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e534b04a7fc64e199e10ce45272cc998",
            "title": "Words Commonly Confused",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I just read a story about a man without a ………………",
                    "description": "Shadow is the picture that forms when an area does not receive light.",
                    "answers": [
                        "shadow",
                        "shade"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are looking for some ……………… to sit in.",
                    "description": "Shade is the protection from the sun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "shade",
                        "shadow"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was not a ……………… thing to do.",
                    "description": "If something is sensible, it makes common sense.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sensible",
                        "sensitive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. me to pay the bills.",
                    "description": "To remind someone is to make them remember.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Remind",
                        "Remember"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You make me ……………… my mother.",
                    "description": "To remind is to make someone remember. The above sentence can also be written as:\r\nYou remind me of my mother.",
                    "answers": [
                        "remember",
                        "remind"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who discovered the ………………. of gravitation?",
                    "description": "A principle is a law or rule.",
                    "answers": [
                        "principle",
                        "principal"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have the ………………… to visit Dubai next year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "possibility",
                        "opportunity"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a/an ……………….. of my visiting Dubai next year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "possibility",
                        "opportunity"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. the books on the table.",
                    "description": "To lay is to put down something carefully. Laid is its past tense form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "lain",
                        "lied",
                        "laid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will see you ……………… a few days.",
                    "description": "With a time expression, we use ‘in’ to mean ‘after now’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "later"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has a ………………….. way of walking.",
                    "description": "Funny is something that makes you laugh.",
                    "answers": [
                        "fun",
                        "funny"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be staying …………….. the weekend.",
                    "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that continues up to a certain moment. We use by to say that an event will happen at or before a future moment.",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}